If you were to go to your local coffee
shop,
you could have a chat with the owner,
or you could just go in there,
chat to the staff.
"I want to buy 100 coffees,
please." "Cool. What's a coffee? £3.50.
£350." You're going to pay for it with
your business debit card.
You could ask for an invoice
if you wanted.
And you say, "Look,
the next 100 people
that come in for a coffee, I want to buy
their coffee.
And all I want them to do in return
is to take a flyer.
They don't even have to get in contact
with me.
That's the deal." So then as people come
into the local cafe and they go, "Oh,
yeah, flat white, please." "Oh, actually,
could I get a flat white and an
Americano?" "Sure." "Oh, by the way,
a local coach came in this morning.
He said he'll pay for your coffees,"
or she'll pay for your coffees,
"just got to
take a flyer." "What?" "Yeah. He came in,
he bought 100 coffees." "Oh, okay." Get
the flyer. Thanks. Someone
paid for my petrol the other day.
Max Cleans. I need to message him.
I said, "Bro, do you know what?
I'm going to give you tickets to Chris's
live show.
I'm going to send you Neutonic
when it lands in Australia,
and I'm going to take
your mom out for a drive." His return on
investment of paying for my flipping
petrol is tenfold. If someone
was to sneak attack me
and buy me a coffee, I would
100% be contacting that person,
just through the law of reciprocity.
I like it.
I had a lad come knock on my door wanting
to clean my car. He cleaned my car.
He's now in my mentorship.
He did 80K in a month recently.
That's AUD, so that's £40,000 in a month.